http://www.blessedearth.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

Business Info Blessed Earth Pty Ltd ABN: 78626772969
Shop 07 5494 2189 Shop 07 5429 6557 Head Office 07 5429 6811
Address74 Maple StMalenyQld 4552 Australia Business Hours9.00 - 1.00 Monday - Sunday
Contact us
Send
Wool Bedding MattressesToppersQuilts / DoonasPillowsCotton Bedding Sheet SetsQuilt / Doona Cover SetsCommercial Bed LinenFitted SheetsProtectorsPillow CasesBaby BeddingCotton Clothing Baby Organic ClothingChildrens Organic ClothingLadies Organic ClothingMens Organic ClothingHome Furnishings TowelsMosquito NetsCurtainsBlanketsBagsTableOrganic Carpet Persian Rugs Organic Wool RugsOrganic Cotton RugsHealth Body CareHomeopathics Individual Remedies 1st Aid CombinationsEssential OilsStemtechTeslaHomewares KitchenCookwareKnivesWater PurifiersFurniture BedsBrushesGardenLaundryCandlesPets & ToysInformation Organic Wool Bedding InformationOrganic Cotton Bedding InformationOrganic Cotton Clothing InformationOrganic Rugs & Carpets InformationOrganic Lifestyle InformationWoolmark ReportNatural MaterialsToxic Free LivingAbout About Blessed EarthCertification DetailsPackagingTestimonialsFAQTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyStockistsContact Us
Business Info Blessed Earth Pty Ltd ABN: 78626772969
Shop 07 5494 2189 Shop 07 5429 6557 Head Office 07 5429 6811
Address74 Maple StMalenyQld 4552 Australia Business Hours9.00 - 1.00 Monday - Sunday
Skip to content
Submit
Close search
Privacy Policy
Blessed Earth are fully committed to respecting your privacy. The following Privacy Policy has been published to provide a clear and concise outline of how and when personal information is collected, stored, and distributed by Blessed Earth.
Blessed Earth is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 and the National Privacy Principles set by the Federal Privacy Commissioner. For more information, visit www.privacy.gov.au.
Collection of personal information
Blessed Earth often collects limited identifiable information such as title, name, contact details (address, phone and fax) and e-mail address. We only collect personal information when you knowingly provide it. For example, we may request personal information from you when you:
order goods that require delivery;
contact us for further information;
participate in surveys and other types of research;
enter a promotion, sweepstake, or contest hosted by Blessed Earth;
register your details on our web site;
apply for a franchise;
ask for a quote to be prepared;
express interest in a particular Blessed Earth service; or submit a job application or resume We do not collect information about anyone's political or religious beliefs, ethnic background or sexual preferences.
Other information we may collect
For statistical purposes we collect anonymous information on web site activity (such as top pages viewed, the number of pages viewed, the number of sessions, most popular session times). We use this data to evaluate our web site performance and to improve the content we display to you. You may have heard of "cookies" which are small amounts of information sent from a web server to a web browser. A cookie's main objective is to identify users and personalise their visit by customising web pages. At Snooze, we do not use cookies for collecting user information from the site. To evaluate the effectiveness of our online advertising, we may use third parties to collect statistical data. No personal information is collected on these occasions.
How we use your information
Blessed Earth uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, Blessed Earth uses personal information:
To complete a transaction.
To deal with your queries or customer service issues promptly. We may also keep information on your communications with our customer service representatives.
To keep you up-to-date with products, services, events or promotions we think would be of particular interest. We may also tell you about products and services of other organisations we think may be of particular interest.
For planning, product development or research purposes.
In the case of direct marketing, you will be able to "opt-out" at any time.
Use and disclosure of personal information
Individual franchisees, company stores and related business entities of Snooze are entitled to share your personal information with each other for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. We will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
We have your consent to share the information;
We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested;
We need to send your information to companies that work on behalf of Blessed Earth who are contracted to perform parts of their service delivery. Examples of such organisations include mailing houses, IT service providers, Blessed Earth service providers (e.g. assemblers, repairers), web developers, marketing agencies, finance companies; or
We are required or authorised by law to disclose certain information. Such information remains the property of Blessed Earth at all times.
Quality of personal information
Blessed Earth's goal is to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. To assist us with this, please contact the Privacy Officer at Blessed Earth Customer Service if any of the details you have provided change. Further, if you believe that the information we have about you is not accurate, contact us and we will use all reasonable effort to correct the information. No fee applies to correction of personal information.
Third-Party Web Sites
Links to third party web sites on www.blessedearth.com.au are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave Blessed Earth's site. Blessed Earth is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy.
Access to personal information
Should you wish to access your personal information, please contact the Privacy Officer (see details below). A $25 administration fee will be charged for the retrieval of any personal information.
Security
Blessed Earth is committed to ensuring the security of your information and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Blessed Earth is not responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. Changes to this statement Blessed Earth may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. We will publish those changes on our web site.
Contact Privacy Officer c/- Blessed Earth 23 Bunya St Maleny QLD 4552 Phone: + 61 7 54296811
